Guide to the Carole Hyatt Papers 1947-2006 (bulk, 1980s-1990s) MS 3105
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Audiotapes, 1975-2003, undated; 8 Linear feet
  - Subseries III.A. Audiotapes, Digitized, 1975-2003, undated; 6 Linear feet (457 cassette tapes in 6 boxes; 1.09 terabytes of digital files)
    - Fredricks, Devon (1 tape/2 files), 1985 June 1 (Box T3, Item 228)
      "35 yrs" Labeled on both sides of tape. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Sietz, Kathryn (1 tape/2 files), 1985 June 5 (Box T4, Item 313)
      "Side 1 only" Digital file spells the name as Kathrin. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Esman, Aaron (Dr.) (1 tape/2 files), 1985 June 13 (Box T2, Item 141)
      "Poyne Whitney." "1/8 side 2" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Arledge, Ann (1 tape/2 files), 1985 June 17 (Box T3, Item 177)
      "'Despair[?] choices'. Side one only" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Avery, Jeanne (1 tape/2 files), 1985 June 18 (Box T3, Item 179)
      On side 1: "Intv. Part 1." On side 2:"Full side. 'Asking'."[Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Kievman, Beverly (1 tape/2 files), 1985 June 19 (Box T3, Item 233)
      "Failure." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Schriebman[?], Cindy (1 tape/2 files), 1985 June 27 (Box T5, Item 367)
      "28" "failure." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Dwyer, Mickey (1 tape/2 files), 1985 July 25 (Box T2, Item 138)
      "1 side only. Failure. Firings. Preparation[?]" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Women's Focus Group Session (2 tapes/4 files), 1985 July 29 (Box T4, Item 272-273)
      Labeled on three sides of two tapes. One notation appears to be "yng" perhaps suggesting this is a young women's group. Side 1 label also includes note "women failure vs. men failure." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Winston, Basil (1 tape/2 files), 1985 August 9 (Box T5, Item 379)
      Labeled on both sides of tape. Possibly continued on Winston item 396. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Winston, Basil (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 396)
      Labeled only on first side as "Side 3." Possibly continuation of Winston item 379.
    - Winston, Basil (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 307)
      "survivors in corp." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Winston, Dorothea (1 tape/2 files), 1985 August 11 (Box T5, Item 378)
      Labeled on both sides of tape, with second side noted as "1/2 side." During digitization, the file name used "Dorthea" rather than "Dorothea." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Zucker, Elaina (1 tape/2 files), 1985 August 12 (Box T6, Item 400)
      "side 1 only." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - White, Ess (Dr); Riggs, Austen (1 tape/2 files), 1985 August 15 (Box T5, Item 355)
      Label indicates Ess White is on side 1 and on 1/2 of side 2, and that Riggs is on side 1. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Melluzzo, Richard (Dr.) (1 tape/2 files), 1985 August 16 (Box T1, Item 005)
      "Admin Dir.--Family Cntr Berkshi[re]." Possibly continues with Melluzzo item 439. [On index, re: getting older]
    - Melluzzo, Richard (Dr) (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 439)
      Labeled on both sides as "side 3." Possibly is continuation of Melluzzo item 005. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Keep, Janet (Dr) (1 tape/2 files), 1985 August 22 (Box T6, Item 421)
      Labeled on both sides of tape, with second side noted as "1/2 side." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Darnall, Debra (1 tape/2 files), 1985 August 30 (Box T2, Item 132)
      "Akron, Ohio" "25" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Tully, Mary Jean (1 tape/2 files), 1985 September 8 (Box T5, Item 332)
      "Marymount Manhattan College" "mid life" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Hamlin, Sonya (1 tape/2 files), 1985 September 9 (Box T4, Item 310)
      Labeled on both sides of tape, with side 2 labeled "full side." Side 2 also notes "continued on side 3"; see Hamlin item 440 for likely continuation. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Hamlin, Sonya (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 440)
      "Side 3." See Hamlin item 310 for likely Sides 1 and 2.
    - Schor, Howard (1 tape/2 files), 1985 September 11 (Box T5, Item 366)
      Labeled on both sides of tape. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Siple, Molly (2 tapes/4 files), 1985 September 15 (Box T5, Item 336-337)
      Labeled on three sides of two tapes; second side of first tape noted "full side." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Garcia, Susan (1 tape/2 files), 1985 September 16 (Box T3, Item 219)
      "Outplacement. Acumen, Resources" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Hyatt, Carole and Linda (1 tape/2 files), 1985 September 19 (Box T1, Item 050)
      "Possibilities/child song. Reinterpretation/self esteem. Reality. Assessing accurately failures made." [On index, re: radio interviews]
    - Men's Focus Group (1 tape/2 files), 1985 September 19 (Box T5, Item 375)
      Labeled on both sides of tape. See also item 408-409. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Men's Focus Group (2 tapes/4 files), 1985 September 19 (Box T6, Item 408-409)
      Labeled on all four sides of two tapes. See also item 375. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Parks [or Park], Alexis (3 tapes/6 files), 1985 September 19 (Box T5, Item 356-358)
      Labeled on all six sides of three tapes; sixth side noted as "1/2 side." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Brown, David (1 tape/2 files), 1985 September 20 (Box T3, Item 185)
    - MacKay, Joseph (1 tape/2 files), 1985 September 23 (Box T6, Item 429)
      "Director. Outplacement. Guidance Counselor" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Fitzgibbon, Maria Halpern (1 tape/2 files), 1985 September 25 (Box T3, Item 210)
      Side 1: "ripple affect of husband's failure." Side 2: "ripple affect-sex-own work." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Asch, Esther Ann (1 tape/2 files), 1985 September 27 (Box T3, Item 176)
      "Outplacement process. Side 1 only" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Soliman, Patricia (1 tape/2 files), 1985 October 1 (Box T5, Item 388)
      Labeled on both sides of the tape. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Gray, Thomas A. (1 tape/2 files), 1985 October 2 (Box T6, Item 436)
      "Chief Economist" "Small Biz [Business] Admin, Washington." Labeled on both sides of the tape. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Garfield, Charles; Nash, John; Sisco, Jean; O'Shea, Lynn (1 tape/2 files), 1985 October 4 (Box T1, Item 051)
      "NWF Washington DC." Garfield: "luncheon speech, side 1." Nash: "president, Nat'l Ass. Corp Dir." Sisco: "Importer." O'Shea: [illegible 2 words] [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Walker, Nancy (1 tape/2 files), 1985 November 26 (Box T6, Item 402)
      Labeled on both sides of tape, with second side noted as "3/4 side." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Fitzgibbon, Tom (1 tape/2 files), 1985 November 27 (Box T3, Item 213)
      "2nd interview" Both sides labeled. Side 2: "1/2 side" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Paul, Celia (1 tape/2 files), 1985 December 4 (Box T5, Item 373)
      "career counselor" "faulty tape, 1/4 tape only." See also items 371 and 372. (There appears to be a disconnect between the numbering of the physical tape, 373, and the digital file, 371.) [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Paul, Celia (1 tape/2 files), 1985 December 10 (Box T5, Item 371)
      Labeled as side 1 and side 2 of "2nd taping"; see items 372 and 373. (There appears to be a disconnect between the numbering of the physical tape, 371, and the digital file, 372.) [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Paul, Celia; Weiss Richard (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 372)
      Label on side 1 of tape: "Celia Paul-Side 2. 1/4 tape - summary Richard Weiss." No label on second side. Unclear what relation the tape has to Paul items 371 and 373. Weiss portion perhaps relates to Weiss item 381. (There appears to be a disconnect between the numbering of the physical tape, 372, and the digital file, 373.) [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Weiss, Richard (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 381)
      Labeled on both sides of tape. Possibly relates to the Weiss portion of item 372. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Rosen, Jeffrey (1 tape/2 files), 1985 December 26 (Box T5, Item 325)
      Both sides labeled, with the second side noted as "3/4." Both sides are also noted with "NG" perhaps indicating "no good" for some reason. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Larsen, Earnie. Stage II Recovery, Habits and Change (1 tape/2 files), 1986 (Box T2, Item 091)
      ommercial product by Earnie Larsen. Labeled as tape 3. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Detroit Women's Focus Group (2 tapes/4 files), 1986 January 30 (Box T2, Item 133-134)
      Labeled on all 4 sides of two tapes. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Cronkite, Walter (1 tape/2 files), 1986 April 9 (Box T2, Item 137)
      "20 min." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Hyatt, Carole (1 tape/2 files), 1986 April 27 (Box T1, Item 058)
    - Glankoff, Mort (1 tape/2 files), 1986 July 25 (Box T2, Item 084)
      [On index re: winning couples]
    - Horwitt, Hank (1 tape/2 files), 1986 August 4 (Box T3, Item 227)
      Side 1: "'Not follow instincts'. Personal rationalization" Side 2: "Summary about middle." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Scudder, Marian (2 tapes/4 files), 1986 September 18 (Box T1, Item 070-071)
      On tape 1: "S.F. 2 full sides." On tape 2: "3rd side: 1/2." [On index re: winning couples]
    - Garth, David. Talk (1 tape/2 files), 1986 October 14 (Box T1, Item 045)
      "10/14/86 - 3:45 pm." An obscure label appears to read "Hy Field." [On index, re: radio interviews]
    - Frenkel, Nama (1 tape/2 files), 1986 November 14 (Box T2, Item 083)
      "Denver, Colo. Full A & B." [On index re: winning couples]
    - Lee, Valas [or Valas, Lee] (1 tape/2 files), 1986 November 15 (Box T1, Item 067)
      "Social behaviorist. Nadir. Personal story. Almost divorce." [On index re: winning couples]
    - Grode, Marilyn (1 tape/2 files), 1987 January 7 (Box T1, Item 074)
      "Side 2: 3/4 of tape"
    - Karsch, Elaine (1 tape/2 files), 1987 February (Box T1, Item 048)
      Tape from "In-touch Networks: the radio newsstand for the print handicapped"
    - Hall, Mary Anna and Craig (1 tape/2 files), 1987 April (Box T1, Item 073)
      Label on tape: "Dallas. No notes. Release on head. Not sure if picked up." Notes on outer wrap: "6 yr age dif. She-fearful. They wld look to dif after she turned 40. He wld have a mid life crisis & leave her for ynger woman." "He very rich, very mature. His mother & father same 6 yr age dif. He always ass. w/older people." [On index re: winning couples]
    - Larry King Show. Carole Hyatt. Dick Cavett Host 12-1 (1 tape/2 files), 1987 May 1 (Box T1, Item 063)
      Tape from the Mutual Broadcasting System.
    - Hyatt, Edward and June; Letters (1 tape/2 files), 1987 June (Box T1, Item 072)
      Side 1 label: "Edward and June Hyatt. 6/87. 'Loss'." Side 2 label: "Letters. 6/5/87." [On index re: winning couples]
    - Fink, Shelly; Getsinger(?), Ann (1 tape/2 files), 1987 July 13 (Box T2, Item 082)
      "2 sides." [On index re: winning couples]
    - Havley, Deana (1 tape/2 files), 1987 November (Box T1, Item 047)
      "Back up career. 1-1/4 sides." [Per index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Bosworth, Phyllis (1 tape/2 files), 1987 December 13 (Box T4, Item 242)
      "one side only." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Hyatt, Carole (1 tape/2 files), 1988 (Box T1, Item 046)
      "Joan Hamburg Show. Smart People. '88. Linda & Carole."[On index, re: radio interviews]
    - Bank, Susan (1 tape/2 files), 1988 February 26 (Box T4, Item 258)
      [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Kievman, Beverly (1 tape/2 files), 1988 March 21 (Box T2, Item 154)
      "Atlanta. 1-1/2 sides." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Wiess, Rosemary (1 tape/2 files), 1988 March 27 (Box T4, Item 284)
      "Denver. Acct. Reactive." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Kelley, Jean (1 tape/2 files), 1988 March 29 (Box T2, Item 155)
      "Tulsa. 2 sides." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Mastin, Phil (1 tape/2 files), 1988 April (Box T2, Item 106)
      "Michigan state senator. Recalled." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Professional Group (2 tapes/4 files), 1988 April 5 (Box T4, Item 296-297)
      Labeled on all four sides of two tapes. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - 25-35 Mixed Group (2 tapes/4 files), 1988 April 6 (Box T4, Item 289-290)
    - Men's Group, Detroit, Mich. (1 tape/2 files), 1988 April 11 (Box T2, Item 109)
      Side 1 is labeled "Side 3." [Per index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Men's Group [New York?] (1 tape/2 files), 1988 April 18 (Box T2, Item 108)
      Both sides labeled. Appears to be first two parts of 4 plus recap. See items 110 and 111. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Men's Group [New York?] (1 tape/2 files), 1988 April 18 (Box T2, Item 110)
      ides labeled "#3" and "#4." Likely continuation of item 108, and likely relates to item 111. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Men's Group, New York. Summary (1 tape/2 files), 1988 April 18 (Box T2, Item 111)
      "Connie, Carole, Barbara Caplan. 1/2 side" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Dean, Joel (1 tape/2 files), 1988 April 25 (Box T3, Item 226)
      "Dean and Deluca. Simon and Schuster. [other notes on label not intelligible]" "70 mins" of 90 minute tape. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Jerris, Linda (1 tape/2 files), 1988 May 2 (Box T3, Item 162)
      "Career counselor" "App. 80 min tape" of a 90 minute tape. [Per index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Jerris, Linda[?] (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 163)
      The tape has no label on it, but it was digitized and labeled as "Jerris Linda" and dated as 1988-05-02, a continuation of item 162. It is not known if this is correct. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Bloxum [Bloxsom?], Susan (3 tape/6 files), 1988 May 3 (Box T4, Item 250-252)
      Name is rendered as both Bloxum and Bloxsom on the labels; name was incorrectly rendered as Bluxom during digitization and file naming. Item 250 is labeled on one side only: "Bordering or bartering[?]" Item 251 is labeled on one side only: "Lone Ranger, side 3." Item 252 is labeled on side 1 as "history of change to anatomy[?]" and on side 2 as "anatomy[?] of change." Item 252 is dated 5/3/1988; the other two tapes are undated. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Women's Group, 35+, New York (2 tapes/4 files), 1988 May 3 (Box T4, Item 274-275)
      Labeled on all 4 sides of two tapes. The label on side 2 of the second tape (item 275) also refers to "+single - Susan Glickman." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Ashley, Barbara (2 tapes/4 files), 1988 May 4 (Box T4, Item 263-264)
      Tape 1 (item 263) labeled on both sides. Tape 2 (item 264) labeled: "Side 3 & 4. Ball. 'Intuitive changer'." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Carter, Ron (1 tape/2 files), 1988 May 4 (Box T3, Item 174)
      "Bankers Trust" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Carter, Ron; Townsend, Alair (1 tape/2 files), 1988 May 4 (Box T1, Item 044)
      Townsend "Deputy Mayor, 10 min." Carter "Side 2" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Whittle, Reed; aka Larzell, Scott (2 tapes/4 files), 1988 May 4 (Box T5, Item 353-354)
      "minister to OD." Labeled on three sides of 2 tapes. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Newbourg, Margaret (1 tape/2 files), 1988 May 17 (Box T4, Item 293)
      "outplacement specialist" "1-1/2 sides." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Zucker, Elaina (1 tape/2 files), 1988 May 17 (Box T4, Item 308)
      "management consultant" "1-1/2 sides." During the digitization process, the name was rendered as "Zuker" in the digital file name. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Goodman, Brenda; Fitzgibbon, Marie (2 tapes/4 files), 1988 May 18 (Box T2, Item 112-113)
      Goodman "career counselor" is on item 112 and part of item 113. Fitzgibbon starts somewhere on item 113, possibly second side/file. The label of the second tape (item 113) indicates that only 1/8 of the final side/file has content.
    - Kalin, Eugene (Dr) (1 tape/2 files), 1988 May 18 (Box T2, Item 144)
      "Preoccupation, Occupation[?]" "Psychotherapist." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Goodman, Brenda (2 tapes/4 files), 1988 May 27 (Box T2, Item 114-115)
      Label indicates that Goodman covers all of first tape (item 114) plus 1/2 side of the second tape (item 115). [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Weiner, Edith [or Wiener?] (1 tape/2 files), 1988 May 27 (Box T5, Item 352)
      "trend expert." Labeled on both sides of tape. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Kiser, Virginia (1 tape/2 files), 1988 June (Box T2, Item 153)
      "Actress" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Weiss, Herb (aka H. Budd Walters, Jr.) (1 tape/2 files), 1988 June (Box T6, Item 432)
      Labeled on both sides of the tape
    - Woodten, Judy (1 tape/2 files), 1988 June (Box T4, Item 309)
      "housewife to corporate VP" "sense of worth thru work" "50 min [of 90 min tape]" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Stearn, Norman [or Stearns] (Dr) (1 tape/2 files), 1988 July 8 (Box T5, Item 385)
      "MD & Management." Labeled on both sides of the tape. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Obadia, Yvette (1 tape/2 files), 1988 July 22 (Box T1, Item 055)
      Microcassette. [On index, re: radio interviews]
    - Lee, Michael (1 tape/2 files), 1988 July 26 (Box T1, Item 001)
      "Australian" "Inner balance. Energy. Opportunities." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Baker, Mary Ann (1 tape/2 files), 1988 July 28 (Box T4, Item 261)
      Microcassette. Date not certain. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Actress Group (2 tapes/4 files), 1988 August (Box T4, Item 270-271)
      Labeled on three sides of the two tapes. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Patterson, Lydia (1 tape/2 files), 1988 August (Box T4, Item 300)
      "Merrill Lynch - EEO manager" "1-1/4 sides." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Barkley, Nella (1 tape/2 files), 1988 August 4 (Box T4, Item 257)
      "1-1/2" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Baker, Mary Ann (2 tapes/4 files), 1988 August 12 (Box T4, Item 259-260)
      Labeled on both sides of the first tape (item 259) and one side (side 3) of the second tape (item 260). [Per index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Amos, Wally (1 tape/2 files), 1988 August 22 (Box T4, Item 268)
      "1-1/4 side" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - San Fellipo, Joe (1 tape/2 files), 1988 August 23 (Box T4, Item 276)
      "O'Dell Corp. franchising" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Sayman, Wynn [or Winn] (Dr) (1 tape/2 files), 1988 August 23 (Box T4, Item 282)
      "doctor to antiques dealer" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Champion, Marge (2 tapes/4 files), 1988 August 29 (Box T3, Item 172-173)
      Tape 1: "2 sides." Tape 2 is labeled on only one side. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Jenner, Bruce (1 tape/2 files), 1988 October 6 (Box T3, Item 164)
      "1-1/2 sides" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Terry, Susan (1 tape/2 files), 1988 October 12 (Box T5, Item 349)
      "construction company. Des Moines, Iowa." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Bellamy, Carol (1 tape/2 files), 1988 October 14 (Box T4, Item 255)
      "15 min interview" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Dickman, Deborah (2 tapes/4 files), 1988 October 17 (Box T2, Item 117-118)
      "3 sides" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Harris, George (1 tape/2 files), 1988 November 1 (Box T3, Item 165)
      "Am Health. Psych Today'' Both sides labeled. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Hafner, Dorothy (1 tape/2 files), 1988 December 14 (Box T2, Item 126)
      "2 sides" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Hartley, Mariette (1 tape/2 files), 1988 December 16 (Box T3, Item 175)
      "1 side only" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Kuhn, Daniel (Dr.) (2 tapes/4 files), 1988 December 21 (Box T1, Item 002-003)
      Labeled on "3 sides" of 2 tapes. Side 3 (i.e., Side A of 2nd tape) noted as "1/4 side." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Westin, Av (1 tape/2 files), 1989 January 1 (Box T5, Item 342)
      [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Westin, Kathleen; Westin, Av (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 004)
      Kathleen is on side A of tape (first file). [On index, re: getting older]. Av begins "toward end" of Side A and continues on Side B (2nd file). See also possibly related Westin, Av on item 412.
    - Westin, Av (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 412)
      Labeled on both sides of the tape. See also possibly related Westin, Av on item 004.
    - Pinchot III, Gifford (1 tape/2 files), 1989 January 5 (Box T4, Item 299)
      "intrapreneurship" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Flores, Fernando; Hyatt, Carole and Gordon (1 tape/2 files), 1989 February 1 (Box T3, Item 239)
      "2 sides. Carole & Gordon, 2nd side." [On index, Flores re: Shifting Gears]
    - Rabke, Barbara and Zinicola, Joan (2 tapes/4 files), 1989 February 6 (Box T4, Item 305-306)
      "M.O." Labeled as having content on three sides only. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Gottlieb, Linda (1 tape/2 files), 1989 February 10 (Box T2, Item 130)
      "market place & MO[?]" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Barber, Ben (1 tape/2 files), 1989 February 15 (Box T4, Item 253)
    - Hyatt, Carole (1 tape/2 files), 1989 March 8 (Box T3, Item 191)
      "Stuck & Marketplace Additions" [Per index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Newman, Larry (2 tapes/4 files), 1989 March 26 (Box T4, Item 291-292)
      "setting up unusual biz [business] arrangement." First tape (item 291) labeled "2 -20 min sides [entire tape]." Second tape (item 292) labeled on one side (side 3): "Larry Newman (Kathy)." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Wesselman, Tom (1 tape/2 files), 1989 April 12 (Box T5, Item 380)
    - Adaire, Jennifer (1 tape/2 files), 1989 April 26 (Box T4, Item 269)
      "1-1/2 sides. MBA. Selling yourself." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Chernoff, Allan (1 tape/2 files), 1989 April 27 (Box T3, Item 167)
      "selling yourself." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Women's Group Hilton Head (3 tapes/6 files), 1990 February 18 (Box T1, Item 036-038)
      "mother daughter" on Side 3 (Side A of 2nd tape; 3rd file) and Side 4 (Side A of 3rd tape; 5th file). Some files are likely blank. [Per index, re: mother and daughter conversations]
    - Incae, Costa Rica (2 tapes/4 files), 1990 March 12 (Box T1, Item 032-033)
      1st tape (item 032): "Carole. Lecture [Womens Group]." 2nd tape (item 033): "Womens Group. Incae luncheon. 1 side only" [Per index, re: women and careers]
    - Wolff, Kris [or Kurt Wel] (?) (1 tape/2 files), 1991 January 8 (Box T6, Item 445)
      Several tapes were identified somehow during digitization as related to "Chicago School Study Interviews." But there is no indication on the tapes or their case themselves that they relate. It is possible that the linking documentation was lost during the digitization process. The tapes so identified are items 401, 441, 442, 443, 444, 445, 446, and 447. For this tape 445, the label on side 1 is somewhat illegible, including the name.
    - Light, Donald (1 tape/2 files), 1991 January 22 (Box T6, Item 441)